## **Keith Black**

Denver, Colorado 80231 (845) 625-9783

## Keithblack4290@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/kblack4290 in https://github.com/Kblack4290 🖸

## **Objective**

To obtain a position at Smoothstack as an Entry Level Software Developer. My current education in Denver Universities Full Stack Coding Bootcamp accompanied by the experience I have gained over the last 10 years such as leadership, budgeting, negotiation, and client relations; will prove that I am a great candidate for this position.

## **Areas of Strength**

Communication • Adaptability • Problem Resolution Critical Thinking • Creativity • Computer Skills Customer Service • Learning Agility • Analytical Abilities Dependability • Client and Customer Retention • Leadership

# **Experience**

## **Cornerstone Apartment Services, Denver, Colorado**

October 2017 – Present

Portfolio Manager

- Manage 335 Apartments in various properties from small multifamily homes to large apartment buildings totaling over \$50,000,000 in assets
- Manage a team of maintenance technicians and oversee completed maintenance work to ensure the quality and service to residents
- Service and prioritize resident's maintenance requests
- Conduct negotiations and create relationships with third party vendors
- Maintain quality resident relations and customer service
- Implement resident retention strategies
- Weekly meetings with leasing to brainstorm, organize, and implement leasing strategies
- Meet with investors and clients to review property goals and improvements
- Effectively reduce delinquency to increase NOI
- Optimize rental income and improve curb appeal
- Develop and oversee the budget and financial reports to maximize profitability
- Consistently reach monthly budget and collection goals
- Maintain monthly budget and prepare bonus summaries, month end reports and leasing summaries
- Oversee and control Capital Expenditure Projects to meet or exceed budget expectations

## eBay, Beacon, New York

**April 2016 – January 2020** 

Online Retailer

- Created, marketed, and managed successful online retail business with over \$3,000 per month in sales.
- Responsible for all bookkeeping, shipping, public relations, purchasing and quality assurance.
- Promote business through social media sites, Facebook, and Pinterest.
- Efficiently managed inventory of over 500 items with constant flow of units into and out of storage area.
- Able to satisfy multiple client orders and maintain excellent feedback rating of over 99%.

# Emery & Webb Insurance, Fishkill, New York

January 2015 - January 2017

Business Development Representative (2016-2017)

Client Service Representative (2015-2016)

- Responsible for developing, managing, and organizing sales.
- Developed and maintained prospect & client relationships.
- Made 100 daily outbound cold calls to prospects.
- Produced mass marketing emails detailing new promotions and services using Outlook and MailChimp.

- Generated and qualified prospective leads to build up our sales department pipeline.
- Scheduled sales appointments for producers in their specific territories.
- Organized paperwork and computer data in prospect file for future reference.
- Researched new developments in marketing and technology that could apply to company's strategy.
- Reviewed, edited, and processed clients' insurance policy and account information.
- Invoiced clients' insurance packages and co-payments.
- Managed, updated, and utilized company's social media accounts for marketing purposes.
- Consistently met team quarterly and annual sales goals (\$2,000,000 in premiums annually).

#### Greystone Programs Inc, Poughkeepsie, New York

June 2011 – June 2014

Property Maintenance Technician

- Completed projects delegated by management.
- Inspected company properties ensuring each building was up to state standards.
- Repaired any damage done to the properties and replaced any appliances.
- Maintained overall landscaping of each property.

## Stop & Shop Supermarkets, Hyde Park, New York

**April 2008 – August 2011** 

Produce Clerk

- Merchandised the products on the sales floor and assembling promotional displays.
- Trained new hires to become familiar with duties in the produce department such as customer and cleanliness.
- Cleaned and maintained shelves and coolers.
- Maintained friendly and professional customer interactions.
- Consolidated produce in the freezer and backroom to maintain open loading bays for next daily shipment.

## **Education and Certification**

Bachelor of Science 2013

Major: History Minor: Business Administration

State University of New York at Plattsburgh

Plattsburgh, New York

Full Stack Flex Course December 2020-June 2021

University of Denver (https://bootcamp.du.edu/coding/)

**Trilogy Education Services** 

Denver, Colorado

#### **Computer Skills**

- Microsoft Office Excel, Outlook, Word, Power Point and Publisher
- Google Suite Gmail, Drive, Docs, Sheets and Meet
- VS Code
- GitHub
- GitLab
- Git Bash
- Postman
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- JQuery
- API
- CSS
- HTML
- DocuSign
- Adobe

- Yardi
- OneSite

References available upon request.